const STORE = [
    {
    question: 'What steak alternative does Chris Traeger prepare for Ron and Leslie when they visit him in Indianapolis?',
    answers: [
        'Portobello mushrooms',
        'Black bean burger patties',
        'tofurkey beer brats',
        'soy steak'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Portobello mushrooms',
},
{
    question: 'Jerry and Lil\' Sebastian have this in common:',
    answers: [
        'They both have Irritable Bowel Syndrome',
        'Both of them have astigmatism',
        'They are Glucatrol buddies',
        'They both enjoy Paunch Burger'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'They are Glucatrol buddies',
},
{
    question: 'At his inauguration, 18 year-old mayor Ben Wyatt chose this song for the occasion:',
    answers: [
        'Ice Ice Baby by Vanilla Ice',
        'Whoomp! (There It Is) by Tag Team',
        'This is How We Do It by Montell Jordan',
        'U Can’t Touch This by MC Hammer'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Whoomp! (There It Is) by Tag Team',
},
{
    question: 'What is the name of FBI agent Bert Macklin’s brother?',
    answers: [
        'Kirk Macklin',
        'Mac Bertman',
        'Kurt Macklin',
        'Kip Hackman'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Kip Hackman',
},
{
    question: 'Which of these characters has an honorary degree from Notre Dame?',
    answers: [
        'Lil\' Sebastian',
        'Leslie Knope',
        'Chris Traeger',
        'Bobby Newport'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Lil\' Sebastian',
},
{
    question: 'Which of these is NOT one of Jerry\'s names?',
    answers: [
        'Terry',
        'Garry',
        'Barry',
        'Harry'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Harry',
},
{
    question: 'Ron Swanson keeps a sizable amount of _____ in his desk drawer. Remove it or it will begin to smell.',
    answers: [
        'Thick-cut bacon',
        'Steak',
        'Pork ribs',
        'Ground chuck'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Ground chuck',
},
{
    question: 'Jerry is quite talented at _____, though usually nobody notices this.',
    answers: [
        'Knitting',
        'Painting',
        'Woodcarving',
        'Sculpting'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Painting',
},
{
    question: 'Tom Haverford is from:',
    answers: [
        'North Carolina',
        'New Delhi',
        'Michigan',
        'South Carolina'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'North Carolina',
},
{
    question: 'Tom creates his own fragrance named:',
    answers: [
        'T-Dazzle',
        'Tommy Fresh',
        'Allergic',
        'Tommy Smooth'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Tommy Fresh',
}


]